<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Conrad</title>
    <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com" />
    <updated>2023-08-14T21:26:16+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Remote Camera Trigger App: A Journey from Idea to Implementation with GPT</title>
        <author>
            <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/remote-camera-trigger-app-a-journey-from-idea-to-implementation-with-gpt.html"/>
        <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com/remote-camera-trigger-app-a-journey-from-idea-to-implementation-with-gpt.html</id>

        <updated>2023-08-14T21:26:16+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    TLDR - developed a camera app with ChatGPT and found it helped immensely with specific tasks but was pretty bad at broader tasks. The concept was straightforward: use Bluetooth headphones to trigger a camera shutter. In this post, I’ll walk you through how I developed&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><em>TLDR - developed <a href="https://conradbez.com/camera-trigger/">a camera app</a> with ChatGPT and found it helped immensely with specific tasks but was pretty bad at broader tasks.</em></p>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>The concept was straightforward: use Bluetooth headphones to trigger a camera shutter. In this post, I’ll walk you through how I developed this website in less than 10 hours with a little help from GPT - hopefully shedding light on how developers use Large Language Models.</p>
<h2 id="what--why">What &amp; Why</h2>
<p>The “Photo Trigger App” was born out of a need for convenience and a desire to test the end-to-end development capabilities of GPT. The goal was simple:  </p>
<p><strong>What</strong>: </p>
<ul>
<li>Create an app that uses the play/pause button of Bluetooth headphones to trigger the camera</li>
<li>Use Chat GPT with the WebDev plugin (<a href="https://converter.app/webdev-chatgpt-plugin/">WebDev</a>)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Why</strong>: </p>
<ul>
<li>To capture group photos without the need to fumble with the phone’s timer </li>
<li>Test and demonstrate how modern developers can work with GPT</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="development-with-gpt">Development with GPT</h2>
<p>It’s always advisable to address technical uncertainties at the outset. With the Photo Trigger App, two primary concerns emerged: potential restrictions by Apple on browser camera access and the challenge of intercepting the play/pause button press on AirPods. Addressing these concerns was crucial for the MVP.</p>
<p>Here’s a step-by-step breakdown of my development process with GPT:</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Develop in GPT</strong>: Requested a basic prototype of the video component.</li>
<li><strong>Test in GPT</strong>: Previewed the prototype on an iPhone.</li>
<li><strong>Iterate in GPT</strong>: Identified issues and sought corrections.</li>
<li><strong>Test in GPT</strong>: Validated the video functionality.</li>
<li><strong>Develop in GPT</strong>: Requested audio playback functionality.</li>
<li><strong>Iterate in GPT</strong>: Enhanced audio playback to trigger events.</li>
<li><strong>Develop in GPT</strong>: Integrated audio and video components.</li>
<li><strong>Iterate outside GPT</strong>: Made further refinements.</li>
<li><strong>Productionise outside GPT</strong>: Deployed the MVP.</li>
<li><strong>Iterate outside GPT</strong>: Addressed complexities beyond GPT’s capabilities.</li>
</ol>
<p>GPT proved invaluable during the rapid prototyping stage, especially when navigating unfamiliar browser APIs. The entire process, from ideation to a working prototype, took a mere two hours with GPT, as opposed to the 10-12 hours it might have taken traditionally.</p>
<h2 id="strengths--limitations-of-gpt">Strengths &amp; Limitations of GPT</h2>
<p><strong>Strengths</strong>:  </p>
<ul>
<li>Ideal for mobile development on-the-go.</li>
<li>Enables non-technical individuals to create rough prototypes swiftly.</li>
</ul>
<p>  
<strong>Limitations</strong>:  </p>
<ul>
<li>Struggles with integration issues and hands-on debugging.</li>
<li>Challenges arise when multiple systems interact or when broader architecting is required.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion</h2>
<p>GPT is a game-changer for prototyping, offering a tailored solution that often surpasses traditional templates. However, it has its limitations, especially with complex debugging tasks or broader system engineering. My journey with the “Photo Trigger App” was enlightening, and as I wrap up, I’d like to share a note from GPT on it’s thoughts of our brief yet productive collaboration:</p>
<p><strong>Capturing Moments with a Beat: Integrating Camera with Bluetooth Headphones</strong></p>
<p>In today’s digital age, the fusion of technology often leads to innovative solutions that simplify our lives or add a touch of magic to our daily routines. One such intriguing blend is the integration of camera functionality with Bluetooth headphones. Imagine pausing your favorite track and instantly capturing a moment, all without touching your phone. Sounds futuristic, right? But it’s a reality we’ve brought to life in our latest project.
This endeavor was inspired by the seamless experience of AirPods and other Bluetooth headphones. Users frequently interact with their devices using play/pause buttons on their headphones, so why not leverage this interaction for more than just audio control? With this thought, we embarked on a journey to create a web-based application that captures a photo every time you play or pause your music.
In this blog post, we’ll delve into the intricacies of this project, exploring the challenges faced, the technologies used, and the potential applications of such an integration. Whether you’re a tech enthusiast, a developer, or someone who loves innovative solutions, this read promises to offer a fresh perspective on the possibilities that lie at the intersection of audio and visual tech. Join us as we unravel the magic behind “Photo with Bluetooth Headphones.”</p>
<p><a href="https://chat.openai.com/share/1c7ecdf6-4d08-4168-a180-862845b6e46e">Link</a>  to the GPT chat session used (be warned it’s messy!)</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Natural language processing AFL injury data</title>
        <author>
            <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/natural-language-processing-afl-injury-data.html"/>
        <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com/natural-language-processing-afl-injury-data.html</id>

        <updated>2021-08-03T23:43:40+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Problem In building an AFL fantasy optimisation engine I ran tired of manually excluding all injured players. I put together a python script that reads the official list of AFL player injuries and outputs expected return dates (based on the estimated return listed on the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Problem</h2>
<p>In building an AFL fantasy optimisation engine I ran tired of manually excluding all injured players.</p>
<p>I put together a python script that reads the official list of AFL player injuries and outputs expected return dates (based on the estimated return listed on the website).</p>
<p>The result is an auto-updating CSV </p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm.png" alt="" width="1390" height="663" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm-xs.png 300w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm-sm.png 480w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm-md.png 768w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm-lg.png 1024w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm-xl.png 1360w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.17.01-pm-2xl.png 1600w"></figure>
<p>(https://github.com/conradbez/afl_injuries/blob/main/injuries.csv)</p>
<h2>Challenges:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Return from injury times are given in the human-readable form (see image below *)</li>
<li>Return dates should auto-update without costly <span data-preserver-spaces="true">infrastructure </span>(maintenance time and compute cost) </li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm.png" alt="" width="740" height="571" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm-xs.png 300w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm-sm.png 480w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm-md.png 768w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm-lg.png 1024w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm-xl.png 1360w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Screen-Shot-2021-08-03-at-11.18.43-pm-2xl.png 1600w"></figure>
<p>* example injury page - not easily machine-readable</p>
<h2>Solution</h2>
<ol>
<li>After trailing a few methods (including painful regex) I settled on the <code>dateparser</code> library converting these times to python <code>timedelta</code>  objects and adding it the date updated - for the full method inspect <a href="https://github.com/conradbez/afl_injuries/blob/main/injuries.py">https://github.com/conradbez/afl_injuries/blob/main/injuries.py</a></li>
<li>Github provides handy CI/CD through Github Actions. I decided to solve auto-refreshing by piggybacking off this feature. Through triggering a code build on a time schedule I controlled how often the list would be refreshed. Then setting this triggered build to execute the above script and saving the results back  into the repo the CSV is kept up to  date for free, without any underlying <span data-preserver-spaces="true">infrastructure</span>.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p>Hope this helps automate your AFL spreadsheets</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Solving the Excel problem by embracing it</title>
        <author>
            <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/solving-the-excel-problem-by-embracing-it.html"/>
        <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com/solving-the-excel-problem-by-embracing-it.html</id>

        <updated>2020-01-17T11:08:48+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    An all too common site, having engineers spend hours transcribing a SME's spreadsheet into scalable code. There must be an easier way, and I think it looks something like this: https://excelanalysis.herokuapp.com/ The context: people turn to spreadsheets to solve their day to day analytics. This is great because&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>An all too common site, having engineers spend hours transcribing a SME's spreadsheet into scalable code. There must be an easier way, and I think it looks something like this: <a href="https://excelanalysis.herokuapp.com/">https://excelanalysis.herokuapp.com/</a></p>
<p><strong>The context:</strong><strong> </strong>people turn to spreadsheets to solve their day to day analytics. This is great because excel offers great flexibility and fast iteration. These are the reasons business' depend on Excel.</p>
<p><strong>The problem: </strong>day by day the spreadsheet grows.... one day finance wants a sheet for NPV inserted the next engineering want to assess a project feasibility. Your sheet gets sent around the whole organisation, everyone adding their own spin, their own logic. Some of these modifications make it back, some float around the organisation.</p>
<p><strong>The outcome: </strong>Thousands of slow spreadsheets, constantly breaking, <em>"v101.3 B CB --change v1"</em>. We've all seen business decision based on spreadsheets like these. Often to codify the logic built up in these invaluable cells the business brings in expensive consultants who spend months codifying the sheet into Python, only for the business requirements to change a month after they leave, making the app redundant. This cycle seems to always lead back to Excel, and it's obvious to see why to anyone who've tried writing a simple python script to do what can be done in 5 seconds in Excel.</p>
<p><strong>The solution: </strong>We need to embrace the flexibility and pace of iteration offered by spreadsheets, not reinvent it. Something like <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK">my mock up </a>gives business users a way to centralise their sheets, allows anyone to access it and speeds up the execution with horizontal scaling. By giving the SME these benefits we could fit version control over it (imagine a git commit every time someone uploads a sheet), and even implement global API's that reach into these sheets.</p>
<p>Excel has transformed the way we make decisions and fighting the human impulse to use this magnificent tool is a losing battle. Instead we should embrace it and enhance its shortcomings. We should enable faster development to keep the user engaged, while sneaking in wider business processes like version control. In the end the only tool worth building is one that will be loved and therefor used by the knowledge holders in the business.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cat bus congestion analysis</title>
        <author>
            <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/cat-bus-congestion-analysis.html"/>
        <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com/cat-bus-congestion-analysis.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/3/catBussmall.gif" medium="image" />

        <updated>2019-12-17T16:09:14+08:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/3/catBussmall.gif" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="50000" src="https://perthcatbus.herokuapp.com/"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Projects</title>
        <author>
            <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/projects.html"/>
        <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com/projects.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/2/IMG_20180830_143620.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-08-14T16:08:35+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/2/IMG_20180830_143620.jpg" alt="" />
                    A collection of some of the projects I have worked on in my spare time. Some are involved, others just an idea I threw together in an afternoon. Use bluetooth headphones to take a photo from distance and a foray into the world of programming&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/2/IMG_20180830_143620.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between mb-5">
<div class="resume-content">
<p class="mb-0">A collection of some of the projects I have worked on in my spare time. Some are involved, others just an idea I threw together in an afternoon.</p>
<h3>Remote camera trigger</h3>
<p>Use bluetooth headphones to take a photo from distance and a foray into the world of programming with GPT</p>
<p><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null">github.com/conradbez/camera-trigger</a></p>
<h3>HStream</h3>
<p>Python library that allows rapid website creation</p>
<p><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null">github.com/conradbez/hstream</a></p>
<h3>Dispensed</h3>
<p>Vending as a Service (VaaS) platform to quickly and easily build your own vending machine</p>
<p><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/NaN">about.dispensed.app</a></p>
<h3>Zerofork</h3>
<p>Using dispensed.app to deploy re-useable metal cutlery to foodcourts in shopping centers</p>
<h3 class="mb-0">Consultant Says</h3>
<p class="mb-0">Neural net that talks like a management consultant</p>
<p class="mb-0"><a href="http://consultant-says.herokuapp.com/" style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">consultant-says.herokuapp.com  </a></p>
<div> </div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">MILP visual optimiser</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">Visual design a system and send it to minizinc for milp optimisation</div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"><a href="https://revo-opti.herokuapp.com/">revo-opti.herokuapp.com</a></div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"> </div>
<div class="subheading mb-3">
<h3 class="mb-0">Cat Bus analysis</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">Scrape public cat bus data and visualise </div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"><a href="https://perthcatbus.herokuapp.com/">perthcatbus.herokuapp.com</a></div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"> </div>
<h3 class="subheading mb-3">Excel analysis</h3>
Get a solution space by running your spreadsheet thousands of times</div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"><a href="https://excelanalysis.herokuapp.com/">https://excelanalysis.herokuapp.com/</a></div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Resume</title>
        <author>
            <name>Conrad Bezuidenhout</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/resume.html"/>
        <id>https://conradbezuidenhout.com/resume.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/IMG_20180830_143620.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-08-14T16:13:30+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/IMG_20180830_143620.jpg" alt="" />
                    Where engineering promise meets business realities to create value Working across multiple industries in Australia and South Africa, I have drawn on innovative techniques to improve business efficiency and support smooth technological integration into large legacy organisations. I specialise in developing optimisation solutions for large&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/IMG_20180830_143620.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p class="align-center"><em>Where engineering promise meets business realities to create value</em></p>
<p>Working across multiple industries in Australia and South Africa, I have drawn on innovative techniques to improve business efficiency and support smooth technological integration into large legacy organisations.<br><br>I specialise in developing optimisation solutions for large asset management problems and designing fit for purpose change management frameworks for complex, dependency heavy initiatives. I have gained valuable cross industry experience working in different disciplines (mining, shipping, government and data analytics) nationally (Queensland) and internationally (Indonesia and South Africa). I have a particular focused on the improving organisations’ way of working through their digital initiatives.</p>
<h2 class="mb-5">EXPERIENCE</h2>
<h4><strong>MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT</strong></h4>
<p><strong>PwC / Deloitte / McKinsey</strong></p>
<div class="subheading mb-3">Leverage my experience to develop optimisation solutions for large asset management problems and to design fit for purpose change management frameworks for complex, dependency heavy initiatives.</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Analytics Strategy</h3>
<p><strong>Global Mine and Manufaturer</strong></p>
<p>Developed strategy to optimise rollout of global miner/manufacturer central analytics platform considering the Strategy, People, Process, Data, Technology pillars in the <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/ca/en/pages/deloitte-analytics/articles/becoming-an-insight-driven-organization.html">Deloitte IDO</a> framework.</p>
<p>I developed and deployed a survey about current state and desired target state at the client's organisation which was widely distrubuted to form the basis for our recoomendations. Using the survey data we identified and engaged key stakeholders to interview and include in workshops. </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img loading="lazy" src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/ido.png" alt="Deloitte's Insight Driven Organisation framework" width="974" height="729" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/ido-xs.png 300w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/ido-sm.png 480w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/ido-md.png 768w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/ido-lg.png 1024w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/ido-xl.png 1360w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/ido-2xl.png 1600w">
<figcaption >
<p>Deloitte's<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/nl/nl/pages/strategy-analytics-and-ma/solutions/ido-insight-driven-organization.html" title="IDO: Insight Driven Organisation | Data Analytics | Deloitte Netherlands" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Insight Driven Organisation</a> aprroach considers all aspects necessary to deliver value through analytics </p>
</figcaption>
</figure>
<h3>Hill of Value</h3>
<p><strong>Global leader in mining</strong></p>
<p>Hill of Value is an innovative mine planning method which focusses on 1-3 year planning, particularly before capital investment. My role was to assess use cases, build user personas and user requirements and explore business use casses.</p>
<p>I also built a demo application in Python to give the client interactivity with the Hill of Value idea.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/HoV-image.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="727" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/HoV-image-xs.jpg 300w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/HoV-image-sm.jpg 480w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/HoV-image-md.jpg 768w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/HoV-image-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/HoV-image-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://conradbezuidenhout.com/media/posts/1/responsive/HoV-image-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure>
<p><a href="https://www.ausimmbulletin.com/feature/the-role-of-mine-planning-in-high-performance/">https://www.ausimmbulletin.com/feature/the-role-of-mine-planning-in-high-performance/</a></p>
<h3>Inventory analysis and dashboarding</h3>
<p><strong>Global leader in mining</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-size: inherit;">Analyse the potential risk/reward assosiated with adjustments of various stock min/max levels in a mine spares setting.</span></p>
<p><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Tableau dashboarding</li>
<li>Tableau prep</li>
<li>Interfacing with SAP systems</li>
<li>Engageing with stakeholders at all levels (including supply superintendent)</li>
</ul>
<h3>Work management</h3>
<p><strong>Global leader in mining</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-size: inherit;">Lead a team to deliver planning, risk and execution dashboard suite to highlight maintenance opportunities on capital assets</span></p>
<p><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Scrum master</li>
<li>Product owner engagment, including design and handover sign-off</li>
<li>DevOps design including deploying AWS using Jenkins </li>
<li>Modern data pipeline inlcluding Snowflake, Airflow and S3</li>
</ul>
<h3 class="subheading mb-3">DATA INTEGRATION</h3>
<p class="subheading mb-3"><strong>BUMA - Adaptive Planning</strong></p>
<p>Design data requirements, colate/verify clients data and process into optimisation engine.</p>
<div class="subheading mb-3">
<p><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Using Python to extract transform and load clients data into a custom built optimisation engine.</li>
<li>Scoping user requirements</li>
<li>Assisting client in extracting relevant data.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="subheading mb-3">
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">CONTAINER LINEAR OPTIMISATION</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3"><strong>MERATUS</strong></div>
<p>Develop software to pull clients data from various internal systems into a central repository to be displayed on a dashboard.<br><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>REST API development</li>
<li>Python scripting, including compiling into an executable to be run as a Windows service</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">ITP BATTERY LIMITS</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3"><strong>BHP</strong></div>
<p>High level design of the Technology function's responsibilities and accountabilities across all BHP sites.<br><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Design, develop and roll out PowerQuery driven Excel sheet to automate the assignment of R&amp;A's based of clients governance framework.</li>
<li>Engage with operational teams on 23 different sites across 3 continents to incorporate feedback.</li>
<li>Design comms plan to communicate new R&amp;A's.</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between mb-5">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">ESTABLISHMENT OF PMO</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">DEPARTMENT OF JOBS, TOURISM, SCIENCE AND INNOVATION</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">DAM STORAGE DATA FAILURE INVESTIGATION</h3>
<p>Investigated various technical and cultural failures in that contributed to a inaccurate data management.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">LONG TERM PLANNING SUPPORT</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">BHP IRON ORE</div>
<p>BHP's strategic planning platform supported by Enterprise Optimizer connected their SQL stack.<br><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Investigated SQL bugs.</li>
<li>Designed platform enhancements and delivered price estimates.</li>
<li>Worked with client to prioritise future enhancements.</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">VACATIONER</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">RENEWABLE ENERGY HOLDINGS</div>
<p>Africa's largest hydro electric tricity generation company.<br><strong>Achiements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Data analysis to determine if generator were aging well based on collected temperature data.</li>
<li>Configure ICS to capture and retain more data.</li>
<li>Assisted in plant shutdown and generator inspection.</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="mb-5">EDUCATION</h2>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between mb-5">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">CHARTERED FINANCIAL ANALYST COURSE</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">Level 1 Passed</div>
<div> </div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">MAJOR IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING WITH A SECOND MAJOR IN ECONOMICS</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">UNIVERSITY OF WESTERN AUSTRALIA</div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"> </div>
<div class="subheading mb-3">
<h2 class="mb-5">PROJECTS</h2>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between mb-5">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">CONSULTANT SAYS</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">NEURAL NET THAT TALKS LIKE A CONSULTANT<br><a href="http://consultant-says.herokuapp.com/">CONSULTANT-SAYS.HEROKUAPP.COM</a></div>
<div> </div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="resume-item d-flex flex-column flex-md-row justify-content-between">
<div class="resume-content">
<h3 class="mb-0">MILP VISUAL OPTIMISER</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">VISUAL DESIGN A SYSTEM AND SEND IT TO MINIZINC FOR MILP OPTIMISATION<br><a href="https://revo-opti.herokuapp.com/">REVO-OPTI</a></div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"> </div>
<div class="subheading mb-3">
<h3 class="mb-0">Cat Bus analysis</h3>
<div class="subheading mb-3">Scrape pulib cat bus data and visualise </div>
<div class="subheading mb-3"><a href="https://perthcatbus.herokuapp.com/">https://perthcatbus.herokuapp.com/</a></div>
</div>
<p> </p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
